(Wil:)...and she said she wasn't sure.
(Wil:)And she strung me along
for almost two years. It was brutal.
(Penny:)-Oh, I'm sorry.
-Thanks.
(Wil:)I wish she had just broken up with me
right there.
(Wil:)Put me out of my misery.
(Raj:)-Really?
-Yeah. Would have been kinder.
(Stuart:)-Wil, you're up.
-Oh, that's me.
(Sheldon:)Did you let Wil Wheaton
get in your head?
(Penny:)-What are you talking about?
-He's evil.
(Sheldon:)He plays evil mind games.
(Sheldon:)-Did he tell you his grandmother died?
-No.
(Sheldon:)If he does, don't believe it. He's not above
playing the dead meemaw card.
(Wil:)Yes!
Enjoy the accolades now,
Wil Wheaton.
But like your time on
Star Trek: Next Generation...
...your smug self-satisfaction
will be short-lived.
(Leonard:)-Penny, you're up.
-All right, remember...
(Sheldon:)-...his meemaw's alive and be the ball.
-Yeah. I got it.